everyone asks me how it is that my
chatGPT is also pissed
all you need is one order
and I launch the agent professor synapse
so if you want it to be much more
intelligent and above all that he really listens to you
and that it is much easier to use
I will help you
and then you will go to the chatGPT settings
you will start by customizing chatGPT
so you activate if it's not already the case
you will fill in the information about yourself
which will allow him to have more than
context about you and your goals
so you will fill in these 2 parts
and especially we will concentrate on what is your style of chatGPT
and there
you will stick the prompt I will send you in your DMs if you comment
your synapse agent is installed
it will be enough for you
launch the /start command to start talking to him
there it will give you the other available orders
from then on he will ask you questions
to really know your goal
before going ball in the lead and answering the question
before having the necessary information
it will allow us to short-circuit the bridle
prompt the basic instructions that OpenAI has
injected into chatGPT
because you guys are too expensive
that's €20 per month not enough for power users
users who really get the most out of chatGPT
who use it for their daily life
for their work
so there it will allow us to
bypass these basic instructions and force him to really
take the time
to understand our goal and respond in the best way possible